{
    "id": "6b9eeda842294165aec0c9ef4a2ed159",
    "title": "Verb And Prepositions Exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "6439859d61c64e22a92cba3f12f40afc",
            "title": "Verbs And Prepositions Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Do you believe ..................... ghosts?",
                    "description": "We use the preposition 'in' after the verb believe. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "on",
                        "about"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She spent years caring ..................... her sick husband.",
                    "description": "To care for somebody is to look after them.",
                    "answers": [
                        "about",
                        "for",
                        "of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "This spray will protect you ......................... most insects.",
                    "description": "The verb protect takes the preposition from before an object. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "of",
                        "from",
                        "with"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He has yet to recover .......................... his illness.",
                    "description": "The verb recover takes the preposition from before an object.",
                    "answers": [
                        "of",
                        "from",
                        "with",
                        "off"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He won the national bravery award for saving his friend ..................... drowning.",
                    "description": "We use the preposition from after the verb save. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "from",
                        "of",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He worked hard to succeed ........................ life.",
                    "description": "Succeed is followed by the preposition 'in'. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "at",
                        "in",
                        "on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I don't approve .......................... your conduct, young man.",
                    "description": "Approve is followed by the preposition of.",
                    "answers": [
                        "with",
                        "of",
                        "off",
                        "about"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He suffers ..................... asthma.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "of",
                        "from",
                        "with"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "That shampoo smells ....................... jasmine.",
                    "description": "Smell is followed by the preposition of.",
                    "answers": [
                        "about",
                        "of",
                        "off"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Please don't make a noise. I want to concentrate ................... my studies.",
                    "description": "Concentrate should be followed by the preposition on. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "of",
                        "on",
                        "from"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "My husband and I can't agree ....................... anything but we love each other.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "with",
                        "about"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Please refer ......................... the glossary for more information.",
                    "description": "Refer is followed by the preposition to. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "at",
                        "with",
                        "to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}